<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome to My Site, Stranger!</title>
    <link>https://omarcloud20.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Welcome to My Site, Stranger!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 21:42:20 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://omarcloud20.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://omarcloud20.github.io/sections/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 21:42:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omarcloud20.github.io/sections/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://omarcloud20.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omarcloud20.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I’m a scalable, highly available and reliable engineer who is transitioning from the oilfield to the cloud. I strongly believe in education and hands-on experience to shape up a well-rounded engineer, which shall result in a valuable asset to any future employer.
I graduated from the George Washington University with a bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Mechanical Engineering (yes, the wheel was invented by a mechanical engineer).
Making a career shift is never a simple task.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorials</title>
      <link>https://omarcloud20.github.io/tutorials/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://omarcloud20.github.io/tutorials/</guid>
      <description>I find self-learning is the most significant and effective skill among all skills someone can acquire; however, there is a need for the proper tools to acquire the self-learning skill. Here comes in tutorial to fill the gap which is a VERY important teaching/learning tool. It helps people learn new skills by using a step by step process, which ensures the optimal comprehension of the materials or the subject.
As an engineer, I have, fortunately, acquired self-learning skill during my engineering school.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
